

 
   //Questions array
   let questions = [
    {
         number:1,
         question: " Philosophy can be discussed in two senses namely ?",
         answer : "Populist sense and professional sense",
         options : [
                          "Worldly sense and Metaphysical sense",
                          "Scientific sense and philosophical sense",
                          "Populist sense and professional sense",
                          "Greek sense and African sense"
                        ]
    
    },
    {
         number:2,
         question: " The populist notion expresses a __ understanding of philosophy ?",
         answer : "Layman",
         options : [
                          "Worldly",
                          "Layman",
                          "Greek",
                          "General"  
                          ]
    
    },
   {
         number:3,
         question: "In layman terms philosophy is ?",
         answer : "An attitude to life",
         options : [ 
                          "An attitude to life",
                          "The truth and the life",
                          "A pattern of argument",
                          "A branch of study"
                          ]
    
    },
    {
         number:4,
         question: "The earliest definition of philosophy is the ",
         answer : "Etymological definition",
         options : [
                          "Layman definition",
                          "Critical definition",
                          "Professional definition",
                          "Etymological definition"
                          ]
    }, 
    {
         number:5,
         question: "The word Philosophy stems from two ___ words",
         answer : "Greek",
         options : [ 
                          "Latin",
                          "Greek",
                          "French",
                          "Hebrew"
                       ]
    },
    {
         number:6,
         question: "In the etymology of philosophy, philos and Sophia means",
         answer : "Love and wisdom",
         options : [
                          "Argument and thought",
                          "Criticism and argument",
                          "Love and wisdom",
                          "Criticism and wisdom"
                       ]
    },
    {
         number:7,
         question: "Who defined philosophy in terms of essence",
         answer : "Aristotle",
         options : [
                          "Plato",
                          "Socrates",
                          "Aristotle",
                          "Thales"
                       ]
    },
     {
         number:8,
         question: "Who defined philosophy as the science of idea",
         answer : "Plato",
         options : [
                         "Plato",
                         "Socrates",
                         "Aristotle",
                         "Thales"
                       ]
    },
    {
         number:9,
         question: "Western philosophy started with which philosopher",
         answer : "Thales",
         options : [
                         "Plato",
                         "Socrates",
                         "Aristotle",
                         "Thales"
                       ]
    },
    {
         number:10,
         question: "John Dewey sees philosophy as",
         answer : "Criticism of criticisms",
         options : [
                         "Criticism of criticisms",
                         "Argument on argument",
                         "Thinking on thinking",
                         "Logic of thinking"
                       ]
    },
    {
         number:11,
         question: "___ defines philosophy as the Logical clarification of language.",
         answer : "Ludwig Wittgenstein",
         options : [
                         "Gottlob Frege",
                         "Ludwig Wittgenstein",
                         "Alfred North Whitehead",
                         "Charles Sanders"
                       ]
    }
     ];    